export const cardInfo = [
    {
        "question": "How many livestreams does Lofi Girl's YouTube channel have?",
        "answer": "8 streams",
        "difficulty": "med"
    },
    {
        "question": "Actor who plays Steve in the new Minecraft movie.",
        "answer": "Jack Black",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Breaking Bad episode earned a 10/10 on IMDb?",
        "answer": "Ozymandias",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the most viewed Minecraft parody song on YouTube?",
        "answer": "Revenge by CaptainSparklez",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oshiete, oshiete yo sono shikumi wo....",
        "answer": "Tokyo Ghoul Opening - Unravel",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "Game of the Year Winner 2023",
        "answer": "Baldur's Gate 3",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fish Intermission! Do fish have ears?",
        "answer": "They do indeed!",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Often compared to Minecraft, this 2D side scroller is known for its difficulty and a particular endgame-focused mod.",
        "answer": "Terraria!",
        "difficulty": "med"
    },
    {
        "question": "This black and white fan animation is known for being animated on about every screen, place, and object in existence.",
        "answer": "Bad Apple",
        "difficulty": "med"
    },
    {
        "question": "A particular skeleton named after a perculiar font.",
        "answer": "Sans",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is that a _____?",
        "answer": "Jojo's reference",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "This YouTuber is known for doing fast food reviews in a suit and tie.",
        "answer": "TheReportOfTheWeek (reviewbrah)",
        "difficulty": "med"
    },
    {
        "question": "This song and its sequal by Waterflame were used in two of Geometry Dash's defualt level pack.",
        "answer": "Theory of Everything and Theory of Everything 2",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },

]